

# BATUHAN ENES BAŞAY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Health Status: 90% Disabled

CONTACT

P: +90 545 528 1997

E: <u>basaybatuhan@gmail.com</u> W: <u>www.batuhanbasay.com.tr</u>

A: Eskişehir, Turkey

## SOCIAL



<u>@batuhanbasay</u>



batuhan-basay



@batuhan.basay

#### SKILLS

**Programming Languages:** 

ASP.NET, Python, C#, C++, PHP

Web Desing:

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js

Database:

MySql, MsSql, Microsoft Access

Operating Systems:

Ubuntu, Windows, Android

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Google Solution Challenge 2020 /

Team I&Others / 11th

- Teknofest 2020 /

Team MEKATEK Robotaxi / 12th

- Efor All Entrepreneurship Competition / Team Pole Star / 1.st

REFERENCE

Merve İşler - Founder & CEO @Fornia

<u>Kadir Şahin - Software Developer @Mysoft</u>

<u>Beyza Sunay Güler - Developer Relations</u> <u>Coordinator @Google</u>

#### PERSONAL SKILLS

Leadership, Project manager, Organized, Programmer, Team player, Fast learner

#### ABOUT

I plan to make a career in these fields by improving myself in the field of web programming. I am currently working as a Backend Developer at Akinon. I always increase my experience by improving myself. I have led and mentored many global communities. I have developed projects in many hackathons so far. My goal is to go further with a company that follows technology.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Backend Developr Akinon

June 2022 - NOW Istanbul, Turkey (Working remotely)

TensorFlow & Cloud Mentor Google Developer Student Clubs Turkey

Sept 2021 - Agu 2022 Istanbul, Turkey (Working remotely)

Growrth & Strategy Lead AugeLab R&D Tech. Inc.

May 2021 - Oct 2021 Gebze, Turkey (Working remotely)

Lead Google Developer Student Clubs Duzce University

Sept 2020 - Sept 2021 Duzce University, Turkey

Software Intern Tepebasi Municipality

July 2017 - Aug 2017 Eskisehir, Turkey

Software Intern Eskisehir Metropolitan Municipality

June 2016 - July 2016 Eskisehir, Turkey

Junior Developer LondonMarketing

Sept 2015 - March 2016 London, England (Working remotely)

#### **EDUCATION**

Undergraduate Anadolu University

2019 - NOW Management Information Systems

Undergraduate Duzce University

2018 - 2023 Computer Engineering

High School Sabiha Gokcen Vocational and Technical Anatolian

High School

Information Technologies - Software

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

2014 - 2018

Dec 2021 EFOR All Entrepreneurship Competition -

Cerificate of Achievement

Marmara Technopolis

Nov 2021 Certificate of Excellence | 2020-2021 GDSC Lead

Google Developer Student Clubs

Aug 2021 Google DSC Leader Certification

Google Developer Student Clubs

Nov 2020 Google Developers ML DAYS Hackathon | Mentor

Google ML Days

Sept 2020 Teknofest 2020 - Robotaxi - Autonomous Vehicle

Competition

Turkey Team Foundation Technology

July 2020 2020 Solution Challange Perticipant | Team I&Others

Google Developers

May 2020 Google Solution Marathon 2020

Developer Student Clubs, Google Turkey

Note: You can check my linkedin account for my other certificates.